{"data":[{"question":"We shall come and see you if we ________ a holiday.","a":"have","b":"will have","c":"would have","d":"has had","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Condition type I: If + simple present, simple future tense\/simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"I often avoid ________ to parties.","a":"go","b":"to go","c":"going","d":"c & d are correct","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Avoid + Verb-ing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"He enjoys ________ a lot.","a":"smoke","b":"to smoke","c":"smokes","d":"smoking","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Enjoy + Verb_ing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Their mother often suggests ________ with some friends.","a":"go out","b":"to go out","c":"going out","d":"a & c are correct","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Suggest doing something.\u00a0\n- Do not say.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't feel like ________ for a walk now.","a":"to go","b":"go","c":"going","d":"a & c are correct","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Like to do\/Like Verb-ing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm sorry, I can't remember ________ her last week.","a":"meet","b":"to meet","c":"meeting","d":"to meeting","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Remember+ V_ing: Remember something which have already happened\/done.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Well, I'm interested in ________ English.","a":"learn","b":"to learn","c":"learning","d":"b & c are correct","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Interested in + Verb_ing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Certainly, It's worth ________ the thesis.","a":"try to write","b":"trying to write","c":"trying writing","d":"try writing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Worth doing something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Now, I think she is accustomed ________ eight hours a day.","a":"work","b":"to work","c":"working","d":"to working","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Be accustomed to (doing) something to be familiar with something and accept it as normal.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The fabric is ________ a material which catch fire easily.","a":"made of","b":"made from","c":"made in","d":"made","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To be made of + a type of material.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"}]}